All-Japan Flying Circus
Summer Tournament
West Kyushu Qualifiers
If you're just joining us,
this is the second day of
the All-Japan FC Summer Tourney
West Kyushu Qualifiers!
The ongoing match features
Dougaura's Man-Eating Shark,
Kurobuchi Kasumi, versus
Kunahama's Flying Fish, Kurashina Asuka!
We take you live to OT, of
which only one minute remains!
Neither player's willing to give in!
Overtime, in this blazing heat?
Is Asuka-chan gonna be okay?
The fourth buoy is mine!
Now, Asuka!
Right!
Point to Kurashina!
Yes! Asuka-senpai took the lead!
All right!
Thirty seconds left.
Stay alert till the final whistle!
Got it.
Got you...
This match is over!
Kunahama High's Kurashina wins!
Yes!
I won...
What's wrong with her?
How can she act like she's having
fun in serious competition?!
Way to go, Asuka.
Episode Six:
"Is That All You've Got?"
Kagami-sensei.
I see you're in great form as usual, Shindou.
Hearing that from a legendary player
like you gives me great confidence.
Hey, I'm retired now.
You're playing one of ours today, right?
Here's hoping for a great game.
Indeed.
One of your players has caught my eye,
so I'm all excited to face them.
Oh?
Asuka, are you sure you're not
exhausted from overtime?
I'm fine.
I could even play another match back-to-back.
Be sure to get some rest, though.
It's Shindou-san.
Shindou-san and Kagami-sensei
seem to be on good terms.
Oh, yeah. Sensei apparently used
to be a really famous player.
Really?
It seems she was Masaya's FC coach.
I hear she even participated in World Cups.
Wow, World Cups?
That's crazy!
I guess.
Okay, so we have Shindou-san up next.
How'd his first round match go?
It was a blowout.
Yeesh. A total massacre.
He scored all his points in dogfights.
Against a fighter? He's merciless.
But that's just the way I like it.
Show him you're not called
a fighter for nothing!
Give it your best, Misaki-chan!
Thanks!
All right, guess it's time to go zipzap some!
You go, Misaki-senpai!
Misaki...
Start taking shortcuts right off the bat
and try to keep him on his back foot.
Roger.
The round-two matchup between Takafuji
Academy's Shindou Kazunari
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Tobisawa Misaki
Takafuji Academy 3rd Year
Shindou Kazunari
and Kunahama High's Tobisawa
Misaki will begin shortly.
Here we go!
The odds-on favorite, Takafuji
Academy's King of Kings, Shindou,
and Kunahama High's new kid on
the block, Tobisawa, face off!
First time since camp, eh?
Yeah. Please be gentle.
On your marks...
Set!
His supurr speed never ceases to amaze me.
Point to Shindou! 0-1!
Okay, let's get ready to rumble—
He's not willing to dogfight?
Why?
Shortcut to the third line! Step on it!
I know!
Point to Shindou! 0-2!
That clawlossal jerk!
Shindou-san probably doesn't
plan on zipzapping.
Why not?
Because he's firmly focused on winning.
You're not getting past me!
Point to Shindou!
Too fast! He's like a blur!
Truly the sultan of speed!
Was taking on the reigning champion
too much for Tobisawa after all?
Hats off to you, Captain.
Damn it!
I can't get a read on his movements,
and I keep falling for his feints!
Misaki-senpai...
Once you get to the fourth line...
close your eyes.
Close your eyes and do exactly as I tell you.
Got it.
You'd better tell me what to do
before I fall asleep, you hear?
Lean down and right!
Now tackle him!
Aye-aye!
One more, for good measure!
Now! Circle him from the
right and go for his back!
Okay!
Point to Tobisawa!
There it is! Tobisawa finally
put one over on Shindou!
How's that?
Misaki-chan's unbelievable!
She scored a point against Shindou-san!
Hooray!
Now kick his ass! Kill him! Overkill him!
She kept him from running away
with the match's momentum.
Let's zipzap, Shindou-san.
Here I come!
Don't rush it, Misaki!
Point to Shindou!
There's the Shindou we all know and love.
He scores another point
with a marvelous reversal.
He got me.
But...
I won't let him get away!
Your back is mine!
Point to Tobisawa!
Point to Shindou! 2-5!
Crap...
Shindou just used the recoil
from the blow to score a point.
The three-point gap has
been restored once more!
Misaki...
It's all good. I can still go.
I'm taking a shortcut.
I'm gonna win and celebrate with a
bowl of udon!
An air kick turn!
Way to go, Misaki-chan!
Nobody can beat me at zipzapping!
This match is over!
Shindou wins, 5-3!
And there's the final whistle!
Tobisawa pressed hard in the closing
stages, but her counterattack ends here!
If only I had another minute...
No, even thirty seconds. I might've won!
But that was really impressive either way.
You matched Shindou-san blow for blow!
You even had him cornered toward the end.
Yeah!
Just a bit more, and this would've
been a celebratory bowl of udon.
Say, Masaya.
If I practice more and gain more
experience, will I be able to beat him?
Of course!
I'm sure you can, Misaki-senpai.
Bounce-back udon isn't half-bad either!
Asuka?
Huh?
My mind was just soaring
the skies with flying fish.
Are you all right?
I'm fine!
I'm totally fine!
Asuka, come with me.
Here. Drink this.
Thank you.
It's really hot today, so
you'd better watch yourself.
I know.
I'll do my best out there.
Oh, you mean your next match?
Before this, I'd never been
part of a club or a team,
or strived toward a goal like this.
So I'm really happy right now.
And so, I promise to put up
my best fight, the way you did.
Are you really the girl who
struggled to fly until recently?
I can hardly believe my ears!
You're bringing a tear to mommy's eye.
Yeah. I'm not one to talk, am I?
Thanks, Asuka.
The second match of round
three in the B block,
Shindou Kazunari versus Kurashina
Asuka, will begin shortly.
Both players are requested to report
to the playing area at once.
Go give Shindou-san hell.
I will.
It's time for the most anticipated
matchup of the third round:
the obnoxiously good Takafuji
King of Kings, Shindou,
Takafuji Academy 3rd Year
Shindou Kazunari
Kunahama High 2nd Year
Kurashina Asuka
versus Kunahama's flying
fish incarnate, Kurashina!
All right!
You okay, Asuka?
Yeah!
I'll just do everything I can!
You're up against Shindou-san,
the guy called the "King of Kings."
Cheap tricks won't work against him.
So...
Go out there and fly the way you want to.
Wait, I'm not telling you to crash
and burn in a blaze of glory.
Your instinctive creativity
is your biggest asset.
Just stay close to Shindou-san,
and trust yourself to come
up with the best plan.
Got it. I'll stick to him like glue.
I'm so excited to see his game up close and
in person. It'll be a great experience.
Remember, Kurashina! It's all about spirit!
Okay! I'll go put on a spirited performance!
Why do I get the feeling that
burning spirit will burn her out?
Tell me about it.
Is she really okay?
She looked unsteady on her feet just now.
Well, I can't say I'm not worried.
Before this, I'd never been
part of a club or a team,
or strived towards a goal like this.
So I'm really happy right now.
But I'm sure she'll be fine.
That so.
Break a leg, Asuka!
I will, thanks!
Well done on making it this far.
Thank you. I'm really happy
I get to play against you.
Same here.
I was looking forward to taking you on.
Not just because of your air kick turn
against our vice captain, either.
Your actions when you had
your back to the wall,
and the way you came up with one
unexpected idea after another...
I found all of it original and electrifying.
I can't wait to see what kind of spectacle
your imagination creates this time.
I expect great, great things.
I-I don't really understand,
but I'll give it my all!
Maybe I'll go all-out too, then.
Asuka.
Y-Yes?
Start by taking a shortcut
to the second line.
From there, stick close to him
and attack any openings you see.
Understood.
On your marks...
Set!
That's Shindou-san for you. He's really fast.
Quit staring and get going!
Right!
Point to Shindou! 0-1!
Shindou has scored the first point.
I hope you don't mind me flying by your side.
Oh? Just what are you plotting?
Now hang in there so you don't lose him!
Okay!
Asuka-senpai caught up to him?
No, Shindou-san's speed dropped slightly.
Huh?
Where'd he go, Coach?
Behind you!
Behind?
So when are you going to take this seriously?
P-Point to Shindou! 0-2!
Was that...
Wow, not bad.
Th-That move just now was the C-Cobra!
Shindou just broke out an
absolutely insane move!
I've never seen it my
own eyes before, either!
Wh-What was that just now?
The Cobra, a move mostly used by the pros.
It's called that because the act of raising
one's body all at once and attacking
resembled a striking cobra.
Wh-Why'd he wait until now to
break out such an amazing move?
He probably never felt like using it before.
Wait, does that mean...
Above you, Asuka!
Above?
You take too long to read the game situation!
And what was that, Sensei?
Suicida.
An aggressive move that stops the opponent
by smashing them into the water surface.
I don't think there's another student
alive who can combo a Cobra into a Suicida.
A-Another pro super?!
It's a combo that floats like a
butterfly and hits like a truck.
Incredible! This is beyond
my wildest imagination!
Shindou just unleashed a
combo of pro techniques!
It's almost as though he's a
walking catalog of moves!
Is that all you've got?
A-Amazing.
That was awesome.
Music to my ears! This wouldn't
be any fun otherwise!
Point to Shindou!
Asuka, you won't make it to the
third line in time from there.
Take a shortcut directly to the fourth line.
Okay, got it.
Point to Shindou! 0-4!
That point widened the gap to four!
I had no idea he was this ridiculously
good when he gets serious.
Misaki-senpai?
Huh? Y-Yeah...
Shindou-san, why?
Are you going to tail me again?
I am!
Very well.
Cobra incoming!
Got it!
He chained the Cobra into
a vertical air kick turn?!
H-Holy cow!
Shindou followed up Kurashina's air kick
turn with a vertical one of his own!
Wow!
Your back is wide open!
Got you!
Here I go!
Point to Kurashina! 1-4!
Yes!
All right!
Can you believe it?
Kurashina used a succession of
air kick turns to score a point!
Here I go!
Again?!
No way...
Point to Kurashina! 2-4!
Three consecutive air kick turns...
Here I go!
What?!
One more point!
You're being reckless, Asuka!
Quit using big moves one after the other!
You'll wear yourself out!
Asuka?!
Her earpiece may have fallen out just now.
Sensei, can't we get a timeout or something?
Well, it's not as if she
can't play without it.
The rules state that the match
is to continue in such cases.
What?!
Asuka...
Point to Kurashina!
Point to Kurashina! 4-4!
Wh-What a crazy turn of events!
A player who only started
playing FC this year
just evened the score against
the reigning national champion!
U-Unbelievable...
Shindou-san's going all-out...
Is Asuka really about to beat him?
What do you think you're doing, Captain?
You'd better change the momentum,
or this could get awfully ugly.
Well, Kurashina-kun is an
awfully entertaining girl.
I'd love to have her on our team.
This is no time for such idle chatter!
You're not called a drill sergeant
for nothing, eh, Satou-kun?
The Shindou Kazunari I
know is the King of Kings,
a man who always overwhelms his opponents
and seizes victory with sheer force.
Please don't forget that.
Also,
it's Satouin!
I understand, Satouin-kun.
You're right.
Shindou-san?
Point to Shindou!
Less than a minute left!
I never knew he was capable
of making such expressions.
Yeah, he always tries to
play it cool and smart.
But that's the real him.
Asuka-senpai dragged that out of him?
I suppose.
She pushed him this far.
You could say she had him on the ropes.
This is the end!
This match is over!
The champion still reigns supreme!
Takafuji's Shindou settled the match with
two consecutive points at the very end!
Asuka-chan!
Great game!
You were so good out there!
That gave me goosebumps!
Asuka-senpai!
You were amazing!
So, so amazing!
To Be Continued
The two of you were seriously awesome!
It's all about spirit!
So this is Flying Circus, too.
Stab before you're stabbed!
Episode Six:
"Stab Before
You're Stabbed!"
Preview